[English subtitles are available.]
The Ranking of Kings [English subtitles are available.]
depends on how many renowned knights does one have, [English subtitles are available.]
[English subtitles are available.]
the population of one's kingdom, the prosperity of its town
and more importantly,
is the king as mighty as the warrior?
Those are the conditions by which all the kings are ranked.
Prince.
Are you being bullied again?
It's okay.
You are strong.
You will overcome many obstacles
and become the world's best king.
Promise me.
[Ranking of Kings]
[Episode 1: The Naked Prince]
What are you looking at?
Stand right there!
I've never seen you before.
You are even wearing a crown. Who are you?
I'm talking to you! How dare you ignore me?
Whatever.
Listen.
Give me your money if you want to live.
Talk properly!
I asked you to hand out your money!
What's wrong with you? You can't talk?
You can't even hear me?
How am I supposed to talk to you then?
What?
"I have no money."
You can tell what I'm saying by reading my lips?
"You can understand what I said."
Yes, I have no idea how did I do that.
That doesn't matter!
If you have no money, take off your clothes and leave them here!
That's right. You are a good boy.
You're helping out a poor soul in destitution.
You're doing good work.
You have a good future ahead of you.
Very well. Wear something expensive again tomorrow.
All right? This stays between us.
Great. Now, run along.
What a stupid kid.
Who is that kid?
He's the eldest prince, Prince Bojji.
He's the prince?
He was probably robbed.
But he's all smiles.
That's because he is a fool.
He can't hear or speak.
And he can't even swing a child's sword.
He's basically a useless prince.
He's not here yet.
Th... That brat...
Is he trying to set me up?
Why are you so happy?
"I'm glad that I get to talk to you."
What? You're happy because of something like this?
I see.
You can't hear and you're stupid.
That's why nobody wants to talk to you.
"That's right! You got it right!"
You fool!
I'm making fun of you!
You're trickier than I thought.
What?
"I will bring more clothes tomorrow. So wait for me here."
I don't take orders from anyone.
What's your name?
Bojji?
My name is Kage.
It's fine.
I'll see you tomorrow, Bojji.
I've never seen anyone like him.
Whatever. His clothes are worth a lot.
I’ll wait for him.
What? You're the prince from that castle?
So you'll be the king?
"I want to be the world's greatest king."
How are you supposed to be one?
You can't even hear or talk properly.
You're really clueless.
Wh... What? "I still want to be the greatest king."
All right.
When you became a king, make this place where we don't have to work.
I will be waiting for that day to come.
He's being laughed at.
This is my fault.
He has been walking around naked lately.
The fact that he might be the next king makes me worry.
Why are you not wearing clothes?
She asked him!
Why?
He can't hear them anyway.
All right, there.
The prince can't hear you.
Why? Doesn't he have ears?
Some people can't hear even though they have ears.
That means he won't know if we are trash talking?
Dummy...
Enough.
Say something.
He's talking gibberish.
Poor thing.
He's running away.
Wait.
You should have told us if you can't talk!
What nonsense.
This kid
has been living in such a place?
I feel pissed off all of a sudden.
He is naked again.
How embarrassing.
He probably doesn't know how stupid he is.
What a happy kid.
He has really been walking around naked.
What's the meaning of this?
Prince Bojji.
[QUEEN HILING, PRINCE DAIDA'S BIRTHMOTHER] Prince Bojji.
[QUEEN HILING, PRINCE DAIDA'S BIRTHMOTHER]
He must have encountered a robber. [QUEEN HILING, PRINCE DAIDA'S BIRTHMOTHER]
[LAW MINISTER, SANDEO] He must have encountered a robber.
[LAW MINISTER, SANDEO]
[THE BIG FOUR "SWORD MASTER" DOMAS]
A prince has gotten robbed. This is embarrassing! [THE BIG FOUR "SWORD MASTER" DOMAS]
[PRINCE BOJJI'S SWORDSMANSHIP INSTRUCTOR] A prince has gotten robbed. This is embarrassing!
[PRINCE BOJJI'S SWORDSMANSHIP INSTRUCTOR]
[THE BIG FOUR "SPEAR OF THE KING" APIS]
[THE BIG FOUR "SHIELD OF THE QUEEN" DRUSI] Domas.
Yes. [THE BIG FOUR "SHIELD OF THE QUEEN" DRUSI] Domas.
Capture the robber.
I'll sentence the man to death!
Understood.
What? That's not it?
You were just playing for fun?
There's no such game.
You are harming our royal family's dignity.
It could affect the stability of our kingdom.
In that case, it is a crime worthy of death!
But now things are clear.
He has no right to be the king.
You don't have to translate that!
Daida is a hundred times more befitting than him.
What?
He seems to be in shock.
I thought he can't hear.
That's what I remember.
Let's go.
Why does he have to be born first before Prince Daida?
I really hope it is based on meritocracy.
Your attire is messy. I'll sentence you to death!
I-I apologize!
What's wrong with that histerical old woman?
I can't believe she's the queen.
Your Highness,
the king would like to see you.
Please get changed and meet him.
That kid…
He has been pretending to be fine
while bearing with everything.
Where is he? Where did he go?
You are one of the Shadow Clan, aren't you?
[THE BIG FOUR "THE SNAKE CHARMER" BEBIN] You are one of the Shadow Clan, aren't you?
[THE BIG FOUR "THE SNAKE CHARMER" BEBIN]
[PRINCE DAIDA'S SWORDSMANSHIP INSTRUCTOR] The cursed clan of assassins.
I thought you guys have been wiped out.
You're just a kid.
Come in.
[7TH IN THE RANKING OF KINGS, KING BOSS]
You are here. [7TH IN THE RANKING OF KINGS, KING BOSS]
Prince.
Everything happened in an instant.
Though the villagers fought hard, many people had been sacrificed.
What is that?
When they saw demons all over the mountain,
they couldn't help but question their fate.
But that man appeared out of nowhere.
His fighting skills were overwhelming.
That was how the Boss Kingdom was founded.
Bojji.
I heard that you have been walking around naked.
[PRIME MINISTER, SORI] What is going on?
[PRIME MINISTER, SORI]
The people rely on us, the royalty. [PRIME MINISTER, SORI]
The people rely on us, the royalty.
Were you robbed?
Or were you bullied?
That doesn't matter.
You're at fault for allowing it to happen...
Your Majesty!
Fret not.
You're a memento of the last queen.
You are adorable in my eyes.
But...
it pains me to think about the fate of the kingdom after my death.
Your hands are too soft.
Daida's hands have been toughened with hard work and training.
I assigned the best sword master as your instructor.
How can you not be strong?
Domas. Yes.
Train Prince Bojji even harder.
Yes.
My son, you have to train more.
Now, go.
Who assigned you?
And who are you planning to kill?
If you won't answer...
Didn't I tell you already?
I won't kill...
That hurts...
The Shadow Clan that assassinates for a living.
You guys were the appointed assassin organization.
You will never betray once you chose your master.
Shut it!
But your clan tried to murder the king
and they ended up being wiped out.
Hey, just...
He hid in the shadow?
Be on the lookout.
Though there's nothing he can do.
How rough.
Prince Daida.
[SECOND PRINCE, DAIDA]
How is my brother's training? [SECOND PRINCE, DAIDA]
Has he gotten any stronger? [SECOND PRINCE, DAIDA]
Has he gotten any stronger?
I would like to have a match with him.
That may be too early for him, though.
Why don't you be my opponent, then?
Me?
That's right.
It's fine if it's with you, right?
Well, but...
I heard he took down Bebin's first commanding officer of the chivalric order.
He's too full of himself.
I'm not very keen. But I'll do as you say.
I'll teach him a lesson.
His aura
is the same as King Boss.
Exceptional!
How about this?
Come on…
Your swordsmanship is amazing.
You will definitely become stronger.
This is the swordsmanship of a king.
I would love to teach him more.
Prince Bojji.
What?
You would like to fight me?
Darn it.
Following that brat has landed me some trouble.
I should leave this place as soon as possible...
You know what?
Prince Bojji and Prince Daida are going to have a match.
Let's check it out.
A match?
It's noisy out there. What's going on?
It seems like Prince Daida and Prince Bojji are going to have a match.
A fight between brothers? That's foolish.
Prince Bojji won't be able to win.
What exactly is he thinking?
Who do you think will win?
Do you even have to ask?
Prince Daida defeated the first commanding officer, Bohen.
He even quit the order because of that.
You're right.
But at that time...
Maybe this match will make everything clear.
The match will begin soon.
Are both of you ready?
Domas's pupil will have a match with yours.
The outcome is obvious.
I won't go easy on you, Brother.
It starts now!
I was right.
It wasn't pure luck.
That move back then!
Darn it!
He got hit.
He dodged the attack and landed a hit.
Amazing.
You're amazing, Bojji!